Mark Munkacsi

markmunkacsi@protonmail.com codermark.dev github.com/munkacsimark

Senior Frontend Developer

Profile

I'm a senior **frontend developer** with ~9 years of experience. Mainly I'm building performant client side apps designed for humans in **web3** space using modern JavaScript tools like **React**, **NextJS** with **TypeScript**. I also have some experience in **Vue** and **Svelte**. I'm skilled in building projects from scratch as well as enhancing and optimizing existing ones.

Experience

SideShift.ai, Remote - Aug. 2021 - Aug. 2022

SideShift is a no sign-up crypto exchange. I was working on the architecture and performance optimization of the app. Also implemented **end-to-end tests** from scratch and improved some dev-ops tasks around **CI**. The tech-stack was **React+Typescript**, **GraphQL** and **NodeJS**.

Coinweb.io, Remote - May 2020 - Jul. 2021

I worked mostly on a crypto **e-wallet** made for fiat on-ramping using **React**, **React Native** and **NodeJS**.

Docler Holding, Budapest - Oct. 2019 - May 2020

At Docler we built a **desktop application** nearly from scratch that operated in a C++ and QT wrapper. The technology for making fancy UI was **React** and **Redux-Saga** for state the management.

Ingatlan.com, Budapest - July 2018 - Sept. 2019

Ingatlan.com is Hungary's market leading real estate marketplace with more than **8million visitors** at that time. My team worked on the main site's architecture. We worked closely with the UI/UX team on switching our legacy codebase into modern component based one. We decided to use **Vue** for building and implementing the new **component library** and the **design system**.

Skawa Innovation, Budapest - Sept. 2014 - June 2018

I worked mostly on client side of our flagship project, Easyling.com, which is an Online Proxy Translation Tool but touched and built side-projects like **web extensions** and small JS libraries as well. We used **Angular 1**, then we started to migrate it to **Angular 2** using **Dart** instead of Typescript.

Education

I'm basically a self-taught developer but these are some maybe-related schools: **Web developer** - Athéné SZKI., Budapest – 2012 - 2014

Graphic designer - Athéné SZKI., Budapest - 2009 - 2011

Skills

As a professional I like to experiment and work with **edge cutting technologies**. I have experience to work on **high-traffic** websites/web-apps and **kickstarting** greenfield projects.